(Howard:)Amy, were you serious
about being able to serve?
Uh, it-it's been
a long time.
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Amy:)I'm probably
pretty rusty.
(Penny:)Wow.
She's my champion!
(Bernadette:)Well, if you can switch
champions, so can I.
(Bernadette:)I want Raj.
Hey.
(Bernadette:)Oh, come on, like
you even care.
I care!
(Penny:)Oh, wait, no, I don't.
Good luck, Raj.
(Howard:)You know, I thought our
friendship meant more to you.
(Raj:)So did I.
(Amy:)Do you think
they're gonna call the police?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)Maybe they'll call Imperial
Officers to take us
(Leonard:)to a holding cell
on the Death Star.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I think that's below the pay
grade of an Imperial Officer.
(Sheldon:)Stormtroopers are really
the ones who...
(Leonard:)Oh, shut up.
(Nerdy Guy:)He's right.
(Nerdy Guy:)Uh, Stormtroopers actually
combine both the function